{
  "decks": [],
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": 1642431517134,
      "date": "2022-01-17T14:58:37.134Z",
      "time": 4958,
      "nQuestions": 1,
      "correctAnswers": 1,
      "selectedTags": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 1642433185938,
      "date": "2022-01-17T15:26:25.938Z",
      "time": 12950,
      "nQuestions": 1,
      "correctAnswers": 1,
      "selectedTags": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "tags": [
    {
      "idString": "1001101 1100001 1110100 1101000",
      "id": 1.0011011100001111e+27,
      "name": "Math",
      "related": {}
    },
    {
      "idString": "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110",
      "id": 1.0001111100101111e+41,
      "name": "German",
      "related": {}
    },
    {
      "idString": "1010000 1101111 1110010 1110100 1110101 1100111 1110101 1100101 1110011 1100101",
      "id": 1.0100001101111111e+69,
      "name": "Portuguese",
      "related": {}
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1641897323103,
      "question": "red",
      "answer": "rot",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T10:35:23.103Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to German",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641897364252,
      "question": "blue",
      "answer": "blau",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T10:36:04.252Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to German",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641897382054,
      "question": "orange",
      "answer": "die orange",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T10:36:22.054Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to German",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641897411251,
      "question": "black",
      "answer": "schwarz",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T10:36:51.251Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to German",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641897608316,
      "question": "diamond",
      "answer": "diamant",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T10:40:08.316Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1000111 1100101 1110010 1101101 1100001 1101110"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to German",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641898588112,
      "question": "function",
      "answer": "A function is a special relationship where each input has a single output.",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T10:56:28.112Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1001101 1100001 1110100 1101000"
      ],
      "description": "Describe what a function is",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641902807254,
      "question": "a TV",
      "answer": "uma televisão",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T12:06:47.254Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1010000 1101111 1110010 1110100 1110101 1100111 1110101 1100101 1110011 1100101"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to Portuguese",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641902836083,
      "question": "a table",
      "answer": "uma mesa",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T12:07:16.083Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1010000 1101111 1110010 1110100 1110101 1100111 1110101 1100101 1110011 1100101"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to Portuguese",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641902852425,
      "question": "a chair",
      "answer": "uma cadeira",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T12:07:32.425Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1010000 1101111 1110010 1110100 1110101 1100111 1110101 1100101 1110011 1100101"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to Portuguese",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "id": 1641902876771,
      "question": "a tree",
      "answer": "uma árvore",
      "creationDate": "2022-01-11T12:07:56.771Z",
      "tagIDs": [
        "1010000 1101111 1110010 1110100 1110101 1100111 1110101 1100101 1110011 1100101"
      ],
      "description": "Translate to Portuguese",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    }
  ]
}